A Guide to the Luther Porter Jackson Papers, 1772-1960
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONAL AFFILIATIONS
  - B. The Virginia Teachers Association Office of the "Civic Education Secretaries Office" 1941-1950
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Page County 1942, 1947 (Box-folder 30:797)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Patrick County 1944 (Box-folder 30:798)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education (Box-folder 30:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Pittsylvania County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:799)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Powhatan County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:800)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Prince Edward County 1943, 1948 (Box-folder 30:801)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Prince George County 1933, 1948 (Box-folder 30:802)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Prince William County 1944, 1949 (Box-folder 30:803)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Princess Anne County 1941, 1948 (Box-folder 30:804)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Pulaski County 1948, 1949 (Box-folder 30:805)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Rappahannock County 1942 (Box-folder 30:806)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Richmond County 1941 (Box-folder 30:807)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Roanoke County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:808)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Rockbridge County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:809)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Rockingham County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:810)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Russell County 1942 (Box-folder 30:811)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Scott County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:812)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Shenandoah County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:813)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Smyth County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:814)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Southampton County 1942-1950 (Box-folder 30:815)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Spotsylvania County 1948, 1950 (Box-folder 30:816)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Stafford County 1943 (Box-folder 30:817)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Surry County 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 30:818)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Sussex County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:819)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Tazewell County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:820)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Warren County 1944 (Box-folder 30:821)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Washington County 1944 (Box-folder 30:822)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education (Box-folder 30:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Westmoreland County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 31:823)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Wise County 1948 (Box-folder 31:824)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Wythe County 1947-1948 (Box-folder 31:825)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education York County 1944 (Box-folder 31:826)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Alexandria City 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 31:827)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Arlington City 1944-1947 (Box-folder 31:828)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Bristol City 1942, 1946 (Box-folder 31:829)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Buena Vista City 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 31:830)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Charlottesville City 1944, 1949 (Box-folder 31:831)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Clifton Forge City 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 31:832)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Danville City 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 31:833)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Fredericksburg City 1942 (Box-folder 31:834)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Hampton City 1942 (Box-folder 31:835)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Hampton City 1943 (Box-folder 31:836)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Harrisburg City 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 31:837)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Hopewell City 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 31:838)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Lawrenceville-St. Paul City 1943, 1947 (Box-folder 31:839)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Lynchburg City 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 31:840)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Norfolk City 1943, 1948 (Box-folder 31:841)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Petersburg City 1945, 1948 (Box-folder 31:842)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Portsmouth City 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 31:843)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Radford City 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 31:844)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Richmond City 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 31:845)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Roanoke City 1943-1944 (Box-folder 31:846)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Staunton City 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 31:847)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Williamsburg City 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 31:848)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Winchester City 1945 (Box-folder 31:849)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Accomack County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:850)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Albermarle County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:851)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Alleghany County 1945-1947 (Box-folder 32:852)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Amelia County 1947-1949 (Box-folder 32:853)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Amherst County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 32:854)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Appomattox County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:855)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Arlington County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:856)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Augusta County 1941-1946 (Box-folder 32:857)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Bath County 1943-1946 (Box-folder 32:858)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Bedford County 1945-1950 (Box-folder 32:859)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Botetourt County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:860)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Brunswick County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 32:861)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Buckingham County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:862)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Campbell County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:863)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Caroline County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:864)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Charles County 1945-1950 (Box-folder 32:865)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Charlotte County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:866)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Chesterfield County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:867)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Clarke County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:868)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Culpepper County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:869)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Cumberland County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:870)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Dinwiddie County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 32:871)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Elizabeth County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:872)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Essex County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:873)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Fairfax County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:874)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Fauquier County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:875)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Fluvanna County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 32:876)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Franklin County 1943-1949 (Box-folder 32:877)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- (Box-folder 32:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Giles County 1948-1949 (Box-folder 32:878)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Gloucester County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:879)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Goochland County 1945-1946 (Box-folder 32:880)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Grayson County 1947-1949 (Box-folder 32:881)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Greensville County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:882)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Halifax County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:883)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Hanover County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:884)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Harrisonburg County 1945-1947 (Box-folder 32:885)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Henrico County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:886)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Henry County 1943-1949 (Box-folder 32:887)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Isle of Wight County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 32:888)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- James County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 32:889)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- King County 1942-1950 (Box-folder 32:890)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- King & Queen County 1946-1947 (Box-folder 32:891)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- King William County 1941-1947 (Box-folder 32:892)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Lancaster County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:893)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Lee County 1945-1948 (Box-folder 32:894)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Loudoun County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 32:895)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Louisa County 1945-1948 (Box-folder 32:896)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Lunenburg County 1945-1948 (Box-folder 32:897)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Madison County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:898)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Matthews County 1942-1949 (Box-folder 33:899)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Mecklenburg County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:900)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Montgomery County 1942-1947 (Box-folder 33:901)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Nansemond County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:902)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Nelson County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:903)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- New Kent County 1944 (Box-folder 33:904)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Northhampton County 1946-1947 (Box-folder 33:905)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Northumberland County 1946-1947 (Box-folder 33:906)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Nottoway County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:907)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Orange County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:908)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Page County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:909)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Patrick County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:910)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Pittsylvania County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:911)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Powhatan County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:912)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Prince Edward County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:913)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Prince George County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:914)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Prince Williams County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:915)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Princess Anne County 1942-1950 (Box-folder 33:916)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Palaski County 1945-1947 (Box-folder 33:917)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Rappahanock County 1945-1946 (Box-folder 33:918)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Richmond County 1948-1950 (Box-folder 33:919)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Roanoke County 1947-1949 (Box-folder 33:920)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Rockbridge County 1942-1947 (Box-folder 33:921)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Rockingham County 1945-1946 (Box-folder 33:922)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Russell County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:923)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Scott County 1946-1948 (Box-folder 33:924)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Smyth County 1946-1947 (Box-folder 33:925)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Southampton County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:926)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Spotsyvania County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:927)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Surry County 1945-1947 (Box-folder 33:928)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Sussex County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:929)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Tazewell County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 33:930)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Warren County 1945-1947 (Box-folder 33:931)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Warrick County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:932)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Washington County 1945-1950 (Box-folder 33:933)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Winchester County 1945-1949 (Box-folder 33:934)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Wise County 1942-1946 (Box-folder 33:935)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Wythe County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 33:936)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Alexanderia City 1946-1948 (Box-folder 34:937)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Bristol City 1946-1949 (Box-folder 34:938)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Charlottesville City 1941-1947 (Box-folder 34:939)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Danville City 1942-1950 (Box-folder 34:940)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Fredericksburg City 1941-1950 (Box-folder 34:941)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- General City 1941-1945 (Box-folder 34:942)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Hampton Institute 1945-1946 (Box-folder 34:943)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Hopewell City 1945-1946 (Box-folder 34:944)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Lynchburg City 1945-1949 (Box-folder 34:945)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Martinsville City 1945-1949 (Box-folder 34:946)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Newport News City 1948-1949 (Box-folder 34:947)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Norfolk City n.d. (Box-folder 34:948)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Norfolk City 1941-1949 (Box-folder 34:949)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Norfolk City 1949-1950 (Box-folder 34:950)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Norfolk City South 1941-1949 (Box-folder 34:951)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Petersburg City 1941-1950 (Box-folder 34:952)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Portsmouth City 1941-1949 (Box-folder 34:953)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Radford City 1946-1947 (Box-folder 34:954)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- (Box-folder 34:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Richmond City 1949-1950 (Box-folder 34:955)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Roanoke City 1945-1948 (Box-folder 34:956)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Staunton City 1945-1948 (Box-folder 34:957)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Suffolk City 1941-1947 (Box-folder 34:958)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Virginia State College 1946-1947 (Box-folder 34:959)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Virginia Union 1941-1948 (Box-folder 34:960)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Vocational Teachers 1941 (Box-folder 34:961)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Westmoreland City 1947 (Box-folder 34:962)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Records -- Williamsburg City 1941-1950 (Box-folder 34:963)
  - C. The Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, Inc. 1923-1950
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1936-1937 (Box-folder 34:964)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1938 (Box-folder 34:965)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1939 (Box-folder 34:966)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1940 (Box-folder 34:967)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1941-1943 (Box-folder 34:968)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Central Office 1950 (Box-folder 34:969)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1923 (Box-folder 35:970)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1925 (Box-folder 35:971)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1934 (Box-folder 35:972)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1935 (Box-folder 35:973)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1936 (Box-folder 35:974)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1937 (Box-folder 35:975)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1937 (Box-folder 35:976)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1938 (Box-folder 35:977)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1938 (Box-folder 35:978)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1939 (Box-folder 35:979)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1939 (Box-folder 35:980)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1940 (Box-folder 35:981)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1941 (Box-folder 35:982)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1941 (Box-folder 35:983)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1942 (Box-folder 35:984)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1942 (Box-folder 35:985)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1942 (Box-folder 35:986)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1942 (Box-folder 35:987)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1943 (Box-folder 35:988)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1943 (Box-folder 35:989)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1944 (Box-folder 35:990)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1944 (Box-folder 35:991)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1945 (Box-folder 35:992)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1945 (Box-folder 35:993)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1946 (Box-folder 35:994)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1946 (Box-folder 35:995)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1946 (Box-folder 35:996)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1947 (Box-folder 35:997)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1947 (Box-folder 35:998)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1947 (Box-folder 35:999)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1948 (Box-folder 35:1000)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1948 (Box-folder 35:1001)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1949 (Box-folder 35:1002)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Jackson-Woodson 1950 (Box-folder 35:1003)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Accomack County 1937-1949 (Box-folder 36:1004)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Albermarle County 1935-1947 (Box-folder 36:1005)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Alleghany County 1938-1946 (Box-folder 36:1006)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Amelia County 1939-1949 (Box-folder 36:1007)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Amherst County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 36:1008)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Appomattox County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1009)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Arlington County 1942-1946 (Box-folder 36:1010)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Augusta County 1942-1949 (Box-folder 36:1011)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Bath County 1944-1946 (Box-folder 36:1012)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Bedford County 1939-1948 (Box-folder 36:1013)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Bland County 1938-1942 (Box-folder 36:1014)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Botetourt County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 36:1015)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Brunswick County 1946-1950 (Box-folder 36:1016)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Buckingham County 1937-1949 (Box-folder 36:1017)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Campbell County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1018)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Caroline County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1019)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Carroll County 1946 (Box-folder 36:1020)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Charles City 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1021)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Charlotte County 1939-1946 (Box-folder 36:1022)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Chesterfield County 1935-1942 (Box-folder 36:1023)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Chesterfield County 1944-1950 (Box-folder 36:1024)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Clarke County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 36:1025)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Culpeper County 1937-1945 (Box-folder 36:1026)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Culpeper County 1946-1950 (Box-folder 36:1027)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Cumberland County 1937-1947 (Box-folder 36:1028)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Dinwiddie County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1029)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Elizabeth City 1935-1950 (Box-folder 36:1030)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Essex & King & Queen County 1935-1946 (Box-folder 36:1031)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Fairfax County 1935-1944 (Box-folder 36:1032)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Fauquier County 1935-1944 (Box-folder 36:1033)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Fauquier County 1946-1949 (Box-folder 36:1034)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Floyd County 1941-1946 (Box-folder 36:1035)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Fluvanna County 1936-1949 (Box-folder 36:1036)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Franklin County 1935, 1948 (Box-folder 36:1037)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Gloucester County 1935-1946 (Box-folder 36:1038)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Goochland County 1939-1950 (Box-folder 36:1039)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Grayson County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 36:1040)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Green County 1942-1949 (Box-folder 36:1041)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Greensville County 1939- 1947 (Box-folder 36:1042)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Halifax County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 36:1043)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Hanover County 1939-1948 (Box-folder 36:1044)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Hanover Industrial School 1946-1949 (Box-folder 36:1045)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Henrico County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 36:1046)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Henry County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 36:1047)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Isle of Wright County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 37:1048)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. James County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 37:1049)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. King George Stafford County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 37:1050)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. King William County 1935-1948 (Box-folder 37:1051)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Lancaster & Northumberland County 1937-1947 (Box-folder 37:1052)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Loudoun County 1939-1944 (Box-folder 37:1053)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 37:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Loudoun County 1945-1950 (Box-folder 37:1054)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Louisa County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 37:1055)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Lunenberg County 1935-1943 (Box-folder 37:1056)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. (Box-folder 37:)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Madison County 1935-1947 (Box-folder 37:1057)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Matthews and Middlesex County 1939-1949 (Box-folder 37:1058)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Mecklenburg County 1935-1947 (Box-folder 37:1059)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Montgomery County 1938-1947 (Box-folder 37:1060)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Nansemond County 1939-1949 (Box-folder 37:1061)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Nelson County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 37:1062)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. New Kent County 1938-1950 (Box-folder 37:1063)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Norfolk County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 37:1064)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Northampton County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 37:1065)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Nottoway County 1935-1941 (Box-folder 37:1066)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Nottoway County 1942-1947 (Box-folder 37:1067)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Orange County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 37:1068)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Page County 1939-1942 (Box-folder 37:1069)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Pittsylvania County 1939-1950 (Box-folder 37:1070)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Powhatan County 1935-1949 (Box-folder 37:1071)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Palaski County 1942-1948 (Box-folder 37:1072)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Prince Edwards County 1937-1949 (Box-folder 37:1073)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Prince George County 1939-1947 (Box-folder 37:1074)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Prince Williams County 1935-1950 (Box-folder 37:1075)
    - Correspondence: A.S.N.L.H. Princess Anne County 1935-1948 (Box-folder 37:1076)